shareyourfreebies.com 2019-06-15

# Privacy Policy | ShareYourFreebies

ShareYourFreebies.com (the “Website,” “App” or “we”) is committed to protecting the privacy and security of users of our Website.  This Privacy Policy sets forth how the Website collects and uses personal information, and is incorporated by reference into our Terms of Use.  Using our Website constitutes an acknowledgement and agreement that you have read and accepted our privacy practices set forth below.  Please do not use this Website if you do not agree to our privacy practices.

 **1\. CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

This Website follows generally accepted industry standards to protect personally identifiable information sent to our Website, both during transmission and thereafter.  We maintain our servers in a secure and environmentally controlled location and protect our network with a secure firewall.   Also, we store personal information only on computers which are connected to the Internet, and actively limit employee, agent, and service providers’ access to users’ information.

Despite all of our efforts to maintain your confidentiality and security, no method of transmission over the Internet and no method of electronic storage is completely secure and we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your personal information.

 **2\. PERSONAL INFORMATION WE WILL COLLECT – CONSUMER NOTICE**

You are not required to register in order to use our Website, but you must sign up to receive samples or freebies. When you sign up, you will be required to provide your full name, email address, phone number, date of birth, and address.  In an effort to provide you with the most relevant samples or freebies available, you may also be asked to provide other information including but not limited to your relationship status, whether or not you ever use coupons, health matters, and your employment status.

We routinely collect and log the IP addresses of our users’ computers in order to enable us to detect unauthorized access and to better manage website traffic, and to detect and log the name of the website they are navigating.  We also utilize geo-location technology to capture and log users’ zip code, city, state, region, and country.  Moreover, we automatically associate collected and logged information with the registered users’ information that they submit. We also may occasionally supplement the information we collect from our Website with information we receive from outside sources.

Our privacy notices comply with all applicable laws, regulations and industry best practices, such as the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Data and Multi-Site Data.  Users understand that the placement, use and reading of cookies and related technologies, and the collection, sharing and use of data in relation to activity by users, including: (i) that third parties may directly collect user data directly from us for their own use and subject to their own privacy policies not described herein, including but not limited to certain data partners; and (ii) that we collect PII that users have voluntarily disclosed and shares such PII and non-PII with third parties in a hashed or encrypted format or, if we include PII in the data, we have collected PII that users have voluntarily disclosed and share such PII with third parties for tailoring targeted advertisements to users on our Website and elsewhere based on the users’ expressed or presumed interests.

 **3\. PURPOSES FOR WHICH WE WILL USE PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We will collect personal information from you for the following purposes:  
a) To notify you of third party offers;  
b) To identify your needs and/or preferences;  
c) To use standard analytics tracking on our Website;  
d) To provide tracking/conversion information about users clicking on advertisements;  
e) To meet legal and regulatory requirements;  
f) To administer, maintain, manage, and improve our business operations; and  
g) As otherwise required by law.

 **4\. SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We may share your personal information under the following circumstances:

a) If you have indicated to us that you want to receive notifications from one of our partners about samples or freebies;  
b) If we are required by law to do so, or if we believe that the disclosure is required or necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial processing or legal process served on our Website.  
c) If we believe that it is required by law enforcement in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or a potential threat to the physical safety of a third party.  
d) In the event of an assignment of this Website for any reason, in which case we will notify you via email of any such change in ownership or control of personal information.  
e) If we enter into a partnership agreement with a marketing company to initiate email or other marketing campaigns on our behalf.  
f) If the information is required by our legal, financial, and other professional advisors, or our web developers when we upgrade or improve our Website.  
g) If we obtain your advance consent as required by law.  
Except as provided above, we will not share any of your information to any third party without permission.

 **5\. ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

To update, delete, or correct personal information on file with us, you should submit a written request mailed to us at the address listed in the “Contact Us” section below.

 **6\. EMAIL REQUESTS FOR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We will never initiate a request for personal information by email.  If you receive a request by email, please do not respond and notify us as set forth below. If you ever believe that you have been a victim of fraud, please report it to the police and take all available actions to protect yourself.  Also, please notify us, so that we can take all possible actions to protect you and the other users of this Website.

 **7\. CHILDREN**

Our Website is committed to protecting the privacy of children.  For this reason, we restrict the use of our Website to persons eighteen (18) years of age or older, and we do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen (13).

 **8\. CONTACT WITH YOU**

We may contact you from time to time via your email address, in order to send notices required by law, to provide information regarding this Website, or to resolve any complaint.  We also reserve the right to email information to you about our services, to provide offers, or to send out promotions to you.  You may at any time choose to unsubscribe (or “opt-out”) by contacting us at info@shareyourfreebies.com. Please type “UNSUBSCRIBE” in the subject line.  In the alternative, you may always unsubscribe via our unsubscribe link in each of our email messages, which shall never expire.   We will honor your unsubscribe request submitted via email on or before the tenth (10th) day following our receipt of your request.  Unsubscribing via the link in any email message you receive from us will remove your name from our list immediately.

 **9.   THIRD PARTIES**

Our Website contains advertisements and promotional offers by third parties.  Any links to third party websites will be moderated by third party companies and will not be subject to this privacy policy.  You should read any third party’s privacy policy to confirm that you agree to its terms prior to registering as a member of its website or agreeing to complete any personal information requests.  If you wish to opt out of receiving mailings from third parties, you must do so directly with such third parties.

Users understand and agree (a) that demographic or other interest data may be associated with their browsers or devices and (b) that such data may be used online for the purpose of serving them advertising targeted based on their presumed interests.  We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our web site such as your IP address and information about your browser, devices or operating system, and may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser for the purpose of enabling interest-based content or advertising to you.

These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.  The cookies placed by our third party partners contain no personally identifiable information; they may contain demographic or other interest-based data in a de-identified form.  The information in these cookies may be linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, such as your name, postal address or email, which we may share in hashed or encrypted form.  To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising and data provider cookies, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at www.aboutads.info and Networking Advertising Initiative at www.networkadvertising.org/choices/  
Our third party partners or we may place cookies (or permit Cookies to be placed on behalf of our third parties or partners) on users’ browsers or email clients while they are using the Website. Users understand our use of third party cookies is for the purpose of serving targeted advertising or marketing by email; (ii) that by continuing to browse on our Website, users consent to the use of cookies for the purpose of serving targeted advertising or marketing by email; and (iii) users are allowed to learn more about and object to the use of cookies.

 **10\. OTHER LEGAL NOTICES**

Any dispute over privacy or security will be subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use.  We will always make every effort to resolve any concerns regarding privacy that arise in connection with this Privacy Policy.

 **11\. OTHER INFORMATION FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS**

As a California resident using our Website, you expressly acknowledge and agree to the following: In compliance with Chapter 390 of Section 22575 of the Business and Professions Code, our third party affiliates, partners and advertisers, are prominently disclosed here in our Privacy Policy, our Terms of Use and during your disclosure of your personal identifiable information. This includes all third parties that we work with.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 provides that customers of Company who are California residents and who have submitted personal information to us are permitted to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  Within thirty (30) days of receiving any such request, we will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for third party direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of these third parties.  This request may not be made more than once per calendar year.  If you are a California resident and want a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: ShareYourFreebies.com, 1540 Keller Parkway, Suite 108, PMB 260, Keller, Texas 76248. Place “California Third Party Disclosure” in the subject line and outside envelope.

Further, in accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California residents are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with the California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R. Street, Ste. 1080, Sacramento, CA  95814 or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210 or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov.  For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit http://www.ftc.gov

Pursuant to The California Online Privacy Protection Act of 2003 (“CalOPPA”) we do not collect nor do we allow third parties to collect personally identifiable information over time and across third party websites and online services. The only third party that has access to data does this only on our website. As such we have no need of response to browser Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) signals or other mechanisms that provide consumers with choice regarding the collection of such information. We only collect data from our website (to provide our users with more relevant freebies as they visit our site). Please carefully read our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy as well as this section related to the other categories of personally identifiable information (“PII”) collected and with whom it is shared.

 **12\. CONTACT US**

If you have any questions or concerns over this Privacy Policy or if you need further information regarding the access to your personal information, or how your personal information is used, you may contact us as listed below:

 **ShareYourFreebies.com** ,  
1540 Keller Parkway,  
Suite 108, PMB 260,  
Keller, Texas 76248

 **13\. CHANGES AND UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time in our sole discretion without prior notice.  If we make any material amendments, we will advise you about those changes by notifying you in a prominent place on our Website.  You should check back with us from time to time in order to confirm that there have been no significant changes. Please note that the use of information that we gather is subject to the Privacy Policy then in effect when we gather the information.

 **14.     EFFECTIVE DATE**

Our Privacy Policy was last modified July 2016.

Official Sweepstake Rules  
Participation by entry constitutes entrant’s full and unconditional agreement to and acceptance of these Official Rules as well as the Terms & Conditions and Privacy Polity of ShareYourFreebies.com.

NO PURCHASE OR FEE PAID IS NECESSARY TO ENTER OR WIN SWEEPSTAKES PRIZE.  A PURCHASE DOES NOT INCREASE THE CHANCES OF WINNING. ALL FEDERAL, STATE, PROVINCIAL, LOCAL, AND MUNICIPAL LAWS AND REGULATIONS APPLY. VOID WHERE PROHIBITED.  
App Store Disclaimer: Apple is not a sponsor of any Sweepstake or giveaway from this Website or App or ShareYourFreebies.com.  
Sweepstakes Timing: The Sweepstake begins at 7:00 a.m., Pacific Standard Time (“PST”) on the date offered and ends at 12:00 a.m. PST on the date stated in our offer (“Entry Period”).  This Sweepstake is sponsored by ShareYourFreebies.com, 1540 Keller Parkway, Suite 108, Suite 260, Keller, Texas 76248 (the “Sponsors”), who are exclusively responsible for all aspects of this Sweepstakes.  
Privacy & Disclosure of Personal Information: All participants must submit first and last name, date of birth and an email address in order to be contacted if they win Sweepstakes Prize. The submitted information will not be rented, sold, disclosed, transferred or exchanged, whether public or private, for any reason without your consent.  The submitted information will be used for contacting you and then delivering the Sweepstakes prize if you are randomly selected as the winner. ShareYourFreebies.com uses safety measures to guarantee the security of your information.

Entry Guidelines, Limits & Eligibility:  Each person may enter once each day by providing First and Last name, email and date of birth to verify they are over 13 at the time of the Sweepstakes entry.  The maximum entries allowed for the Sweepstakes per person is thirty (30) total entries.  Chances of winning will be determined upon the number of entries during the Sweepstakes Period of Entry.  Most public libraries allow for free internet and computers for entry and paid internet access is not required to enter.  You are not allowed to buy a computer or internet access in order to enter the Sweepstakes.  Each person may also enter by mailing their first and last name, email and date of birth to: 1540 Keller Parkway, Suite 108, PMB 260, Keller, Texas, 76248.  Sweepstakes is open to all legal residents of Canada and the United States and District of Columbia who are 13 years of age or older as of the beginning date of this Sweepstakes. Employees, officers, and directors (including immediate family members and members of the same household) of the Sponsors are not eligible to participate.  All federal, state, provincial and local laws and regulations apply. Void where prohibited.  
Sweepstakes Prize Information: A total of one (1) Sweepstakes Winners will be sent Sweepstake Prize in the form of a FT4 Heart Rate Monitor ($100 value) which is not exchangeable for currency or other products and has no redeemable cash value.  Prizes will be shipped within 4 weeks of being claimed as set forth herein.  ShareYourFreebies.com reserves the right to substitute another product of equal value in the event the Sweepstake Prize becomes unavailable or if it deems so in its sole opinion.

General Terms & Conditions: In the sole and exclusive opinion of ShareYourFreebies.com, if for any reason, this Sweepstakes cannot be run as planned and set forth herein or in any way due to legal changes, legislation, court rulings or regulations of federal, state or local jurisdictions of the Sweepstakes eligible residents related to Sweepstakes, or due to the privacy, fairness, administration, integrity, proper conduct, process, guidelines of this Sweepstakes or the Prize is hindered, delayed, adversely affected,  or degraded, including but not limited to unauthorized intervention, fraud, technical inability or failure, by reason of infection by computer virus, bugs, tampering, or otherwise or for any other causes beyond its control, ShareYourFreebies.com reserves the right to delay, suspend, modify, cancel or terminate this Sweepstakes, including delaying, suspending, modifying or cancelling the methods of entry, and the selection of Sweepstakes Winners from all prior received eligible entries at the time of such action.  All entrants are allowed to request that ShareYourFreebies.com or its affiliates will remove them from either email or mail promotions at any time.  
Use of Image and Comments: You hereby grant to us a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable right to use, reproduce, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display such comments and any likeness or pictures posted of yourself or your profile pictures on the Website and on any third party social media web pages built to market and advertise or promote this Website; to reproduce or store the comments on our computers and servers; to make any modifications or reformatting necessary to publish and display the comments on the Website; and to grant sublicenses to third parties. We reserve the right to monitor and remove any comments at any time without notice.

Selection & Announcement of Sweepstakes Winner: The Sweepstakes Winner will be selected by a random drawing on or by the date set forth on our web and then contacted by email.  The Sweepstake Winner will be announced on the Facebook page of ShareYourFreebies.com. The Sweepstake Winner will have seven (7) business days to respond to the email from ShareYourFreebies.com with their full mailing address.  Failure to reply during this time will lead to a second random drawing and same procedure will follow until a Sweepstake Winner is mailed the Sweepstakes Prize.

This is a Promotion of ShareYourFreebies.com and is in not in any way endorsed, administered, associated, approved or sponsored by Facebook, Apple or Google. You understand that you are providing your information to ShareYourFreebies.com – not Facebook, Google or Apple.
